# Mayur Kolki

Seeking a responsible and challenging position in the organization where my knowledge and experience can be shared and enriched. Data Analyst with 4.5+ years of experience in solving realworld business challenges using data analytics, analyzing large data sets and coming up with datadriven insights for early-stage technology companies.

Location -Remote ,Pune (+91) 9881718443 mayur.kolki@gmailcom

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Kodo**, Remote — Product and Data Analyst

Jan 2023 - PRESENT

Metabase Admin, MIS reports automating, Metrics Dashboards, Sale GTV Dashboards, Users Groups and managing metabase permissions.

ETL process python scripts for external 3rd party data sources.

Credit Score Card and Defaulter prediction.

# **Open financial technologies**, Bengaluru — *Jr.Data Analyst*

July 2021 - Jan 2023

Automation of user Subscription repayment module.

Ip address Alerts.

Webscrapping for onboarding completed SME.

Data Report.

### Rego Digital Solutions Pvt. Ltd., Pune — Associate Analyst

Aug 2019 - Jun 2021

Sql query developing.

MIS report data to product managers.

Daily Data Reporting

### **EDUCATION**

### **Nbn Sinhgad College**, Pune — *B.E E&TC*

2014-2019

# **Imarticus Learning,** Location — PGA Data Analytics

2020-2021

#### **SKILLS**

Sql ,Python , Dashboards , Linux,Metabase, Looker, Streamlit, Django, Machine Learning, Automation.

#### Social links

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in /mayur-kolki-6a42ba200/

GitHub-github.com/MayurKolki

### **LANGUAGES**

Englis, Dolor Hindi, Kannada, Marathi